And boys, I've been trading for 13
years. I've discovered something
recently over this past year is there
are two major ways to make money as a
day trader or as a trader overall.
Honestly, at this point, advise you to
not be a day trader. Couple trades a
week sort of thing. Slower pace is
actually the better way to go. For me, I
actually profit more. Day trading is too
too difficult. But here's the advice for
you going into 2026 about the best
things that you can do as a trader,
right? Let's first of all talk about
what does it mean to be in 2026? Is it
actually different than 2025? Well, kind
of. Yeah. As the markets change, the
major thing that's changing right now is
the AI bubble that people are talking
about. US economy is doing super well.
The tech stocks or the AI space is
absolutely booming and that's causing a
ton of upward momentum in the NASDAQ.
gold doing super super well and I'm
assuming Bitcoin is going to be doing
super super well in 2026 at some point
again. Right. Overall 2026 to me is
going to be incredibly volatile. I think
the VIX is going to be insanely high. So
we need to prepare ourselves in order to
be in a state where we don't blow
ourselves up. So brings me to number one
piece of advice. We're going to not want
to be using massive amounts of leverage.
What we need to prepare to do is we need
to be looking at those charts and we
need to be looking at those high time
frames and just be adding to long-term
plays. When things come down, add to the
positions, let them run for longer
periods of time on your personal
account, right? Prop firms is a little
bit different. The strategy you want to
be doing is looking for winning streaks.
So, you're going to be wanting low R
setup so you can be very, very highly
profitable and probability that you win
very, very high. This is the era of prop
firms being stable. There's not really
much for rug pulls in the prop firm
space anymore. All of these top prop
firms that have been sustainable for
years, such as Maven, they have a very
small chance of going under at this
point. Maven's doing incredibly well.
We're incredibly stable. Our risk
management is awesome. And I suspect all
of the other firms that were very
similar to us have also mastered and
locked in the risk management. And for
you to determine which prop firm is best
for you, that's going to be your
decision, right? I suggest maybe. So,
here's the thing. We're going to go
heavy into prop firms. If you want to
day trade, what you're going to be doing
is you're going to be buying as many
prop firm accounts as possible as you
get your pay from your job, whatever,
and you're going to buy a few of them.
And what you're going to do is you're
going to decide on one thing. I'm going
to tell you right now, we're going to
break this down super super easy so you
can get profitable in 2026. You're going
to decide either Bitcoin, NASDAQ, or
gold. Pick one of those. I don't want
you to do anything else. Pick one of
them, right? Because they have
incredibly high liquidity. But when you
look at the same chart day in day out,
you know what those higher time frame
monthly, weekly, daily levels are
already when you sit down at the charts,
you constantly are in tune with the
market and you are going to watch that
chart like a hawk every single day for a
couple hours and you're going to know
how it moves and what the price is at
all times. With prop firms, it is so
incredibly easy. All you want to be
doing is looking for a very low R setup.
You want to be following trends. You can
do whatever strategy you want because
honestly, you don't even need to be a
profitable trader in order to make
money. All you need to do is go on
winning streaks. And I'm being 100%
honest with you right now. The better
way to go is to go on winning streaks,
get a payout, and then blow the account.
This is how I trade on prop firms. And
this is how I make 2x on all of my
investment on prop firms. I have a
strategy that allows me to DCA into
trades, making it very, very easy for me
to get proper entry. And then I
literally just shoot for the absolute
limit of what I can get in that day. So
if I have a 50% consistency score, I
only shoot for 50%. And then I will risk
the whole account basically per day.
Both ways to make money as a trader, you
need to not care about the money. That's
what I've learned over the past decade.
Whenever I needed to make money, I lost
everything, right? And I did a challenge
last summer that allowed me to live out
of my car and basically lower my
expenses to zero. I was simulating being
homeless. The idea of a person who does
not have any expenses. And that was the
most amazing time of my trading ever. I
was making like 20% a month sort of
thing. It was awesome. Some of my best
trading ever. All I had to do was not
need the money. So if I didn't want to
trade that day, it didn't matter. I
really didn't need to do it. In 2026,
what we're doing is we're creating a
scenario where we do not need the money
from trading. So the one way be uber
rich. Lovely. Who can say they can be
uber rich? Maybe one, maybe two. There's
nobody in the audience watching right
now that's uber rich that's going to
have this solution. Right? So when I was
doing the simulation, it was pretty easy
for me to actually make it very
stress-free because I always did have
that backup. But for somebody who was
actually living without any income could
be rather stressful. I don't necessarily
recommend it. But I do recommended
taking some pieces of vice from that
where you do lower the cost of your
living. Maybe go live with your mom. Go
live in her basement in 2026. Like stop
paying rent. Rent is the biggest one.
Stop financing your car. Stop buying
stupid things that you don't need like
expensive stakes or buying dates for
girls or whatever. If you guys want to
get rich, you have to make the
sacrifices now in order to get the
rewards later. So, with all that being
said, I found that being more of a zen
person, more of a Buddha, I'll say
Buddhist sort of person, I tr I practice
meditation. I light these dinky little
incense all the time now. I've got
crystals, boys. I never thought I'd be a
guy that carries around a rock. I've got
all of these stupid little things
because for some reason it brings me a
little bit of peace. All of these things
that bring you peace that allow you to
live a calmer life are going to
replicate right onto that chart. Now, if
you're going out on the weekends and
you're partying or you're going out and
you're going on dates or you're going
out and doing crazy adventures, all of
these things that gather dopamine, none
of it anymore. You're allowed to go to
the gym, you're allowed to meditate,
you're allowed to go on hikes. If you
want to really lock in, this is the way
that you do it is you become a zen monk.
That is the best way to do it. And when
I was younger and I was early in my
trading days and I was that crazy
influencer yelling at the camera with
the crazy hair, my trading was horrible
back then. But now I have so much more
peace and it's a lot easier and to not
go on these crazy high swings and lows.
Every influencer I see online, doesn't
matter how much money they're making
because either one, it's not real or
two, they've been doing this much longer
than I have and I cannot do the same.
The best traders in the world, the best
day traders in the world make 10% on
average per month. 8 [music] to 12.
Okay, that means your goal is to shoot
for five to 8% per month. No more. Guess
what? You're not as good as the best day
traders in the world, obviously, because
you're watching this video. Why did I
say 5%? Why not less than five? Why not
2%? 2% on average per month, you would
be performing worse than just buying and
investing. If you would just bought
Bitcoin and you just sat in Bitcoin,
Bitcoin performs an average of 4% per
month. So, your goal is to beat the
market, but perform worse than the best
people ever. So, that's 5 to 8%. A
realistic goal for how much you're going
to be making here, 2% per week maximum.
Do not aim for more than 2% per week. If
you're risking 1% per trade and you
shoot it for 2 hour and you made 2%,
you're done for the week. Don't trade
tons, boys. I think I told you at the
beginning here, the less you trade, the
better you're going to do. The more
peaceful you are. The longer term your
trades are, the longer you paced out,
you do things, the better you'll do,
boys. It's all you need to make it rich
in 2026. All you want is profit in 2026.
What did I tell you you're going to do?
You're going to invest it into Bitcoin,
and you're going to sit on Bitcoin. And
everything you make this year, the extra
income you make from trading will then
go into Bitcoin. And that will make you
rich because that will that will
snowball into something much bigger and
go exponential. Thanks for watching,
guys.